https://www.box.co.uk/privacy-policy

Network Clearance
Network Attached Storage (NAS)
66" and above
51" to 65"
33" to 50"
16" to 32"
Box Ltd Privacy Policy
We at Box Ltd are totally committed to protecting your privacy. We comply with the principles of the UK Data Protection Act 1998 and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 subsequently incorporating the EU Cookie Regulations of May 2011. We conform with the EU General Data Protection Regulation from 25 May 2018.
Overview:
Box Ltd trading as Box.co.uk. This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use our website www.box.co.uk and sign up to our marketing emails.
What information do we collect about you?
How will we use the information about you?
Email Marketing
Access to your information and correction
Cookies
Other websites
Changes to our privacy policy
How to contact us
What information do
we collect about you?
We collect information about you in order to process your order
and send you our mailshots. That information will only be shared with other
parties that are and deemed as a legitimate business interest. The information
we hold may include:
Your Name
Postal / Delivery
Addressís (required to deliver your order)
Password (encrypted record
of your password)
Phone / Mobile Number (For
delivery issues / Updates)
Email Address (Used as
your login to our site)
Tokenised Card Details
(Limited details to aid future purchases and refunds)
IP Address / Browser Type
(Used for Payment / Fraud Checks)
Product Order / Invoice
History (To fulfil any copy invoiceís / Warranty / Returns)
Email
Marketing Data via ìTracking Pixels / Tracking Beaconî
Recipientís IP address, browser, email
client type, Open time / Date and other similar Details.
How will we use the
information about you?
The
collected information about you is used to process your order, manage your
account and aid any further communication regarding your order. For example a
request for warranty / support with your purchase in the future / Product
Review / Feedback.
In
the processing of your order, we may be required to share your details with our
approved third parties:
Couriers ñ To provide required tracking and order updates for your order, Our most common courier partners are:
DPD
MyHermes
ArrowXL
Business Post
TNT
Finance / Payment Merchants ñ To complete the payment process for your order maybe:
PayPal
Amazon Pay
Klarna
Suppliers that offer certain ship direct product ranges:
Ingram Micro
Techdata
Exertis
Manufacturers only in the request of warranty work on your item we may be required to provide some Personal Data / Contact information. Ie if your product is within Warranty with a Manufacturer and we need to send the item off for repair on your behalf.
Product Reviews - In order to obtain impartial reviews on our products and service we partner with Reevoo who email you after purchase to request feedback..
In order to be able
to offer you Klarnaís payment options, we will pass to Klarna certain aspects
of your personal information, such as contact and order details, in order for
Klarna to assess whether you qualify for their payment options and to tailor
the payment options for you.
General information on Klarna you can find here. Your personal data is handled in accordance
with applicable data protection law and in accordance with the information in Klarnaís privacy
policy.
We will never collect sensitive information about you without your
agreement. You have a right to ask for a copy of the information which we are
holding and we will delete information or correct any inaccuracies for no
charge as soon as you make the request.
We require all third parties to respect the security of your
information and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our
third-party service providers to use your information for their own purposes
and only permit them to process your information data for specified purposes
and in accordance with our instructions.
Data will only be released to other third parties (e.g. the police
/ HMRC) on request where there is a legal requirement for us to do so.
Email Marketing
Box Limited use email marketing to reach out to our
customers / subscribers to notify you all of our great deals. If you also agree
to marketing communications, We share some of your personal information to
approved third parties to offer a range of services / offers. This choice is
offered to you during the signup process. At any time you can unsubscribe from
this by clicking here† www.box.co.uk/unsubscribe
We
use an award winning email client services from Mailchimp and dotdigital to send and create
our email campaigns and below are the main key facts regarding their privacy
polices which we feel are important to highlight and the full details are here: https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/ and here https://dotdigital.com/terms/privacy-policy/
ìQuoted as at 21/10/2019 from above mailchimp urlî
3A
A. Information
We Collect
The
Personal Information that we may collect or receive about you broadly falls
into the following categories:
(i)†Information we
receive about Contacts from our Members: A Member may provide
Personal Information about you to us through the Services. For example, when a
Member uploads their Distribution List or integrates the Services with another
website or service (for example, when a Member chooses to connect their e-commerce
account with Mailchimp), or when you sign up for a Memberís Distribution List
on a Mailchimp signup form, they may provide us with certain contact
information or other Personal Information about you such as your name, email
address, address or telephone number. You may have the opportunity to update
some of this information by electing to update or manage your preferences via
an email you receive from a Member.
(ii)†Information we
collect automatically: When you interact with an email campaign
that you receive from a Member or browse or purchase from a Memberís connected
store, we may collect information about your device and interaction with an
email. We use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect some of this
information. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies is discussed
more below, and in more detail in our Cookie Statement†here.
Device
information: We collect information about the device and applications you
use to access emails sent through our Services, such as your IP address,
your operating system, your browser ID, and other information about your
system and connection.
Product
usage data: We collect usage data about you whenever you interact with
emails sent through the Services, which may include dates and times you
access emails and your browsing activities (such as what pages are
viewed). We also collect information regarding the performance of the
Services, including metrics related to the deliverability of emails and
other electronic communications our Members send through the Services.
This information allows us to improve the content and operation of the
Services, and facilitate research and analysis of the Services.
(iii)†Information we
collect from other sources: From time to time, we may obtain
information about you from third-party sources, such as social media platforms
and third-party data providers. We take steps to ensure that such third parties
are legally or contractually permitted to disclose such information to us, and
we use this information to provide publicly available social media information
about you to Members who have enabled the "Social Profiles" feature
in their Mailchimp accounts.î
Customer Service /
Product Reviews
Box Ltd pride ourselves on our customer service and keen to get
feedback and reviews on our products / service that you receive from Box Ltd.
We share your order details ie the product purchased and only your email
address to request a review on our service / product to help us improve our
products and services in the future.
Our Review Partner is Reevoo.com
https://www.reevoo.com/en/terms-conditions/
Access to your
information and correction
You have the right to request a copy of the information that we
hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal
information, please email or write to us at the following address. We want to
make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may
ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate. Please
email†data.protection@box.co.uk†with your request.
Cookies
Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard
internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is
used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on
website activity. For further information visit†www.aboutcookies.org†or†www.allaboutcookies.org. You can set your browser not to accept cookies
and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser.
However in a few cases some of our website features may not function as a
result. If you would like advice and assistance here please contact at†data.protection@box.co.uk†and we will be happy to help.
Other websites
Our website sometimes contains links to other websites. This
privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites
you should read their own privacy policies.
Changes to our
privacy policy
We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place
any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on 10/12/2020.
How to contact us
Please contact us if you have any questions about our
privacy policy or information we hold about you:
By Email ñ data.protection@box.co.uk
By Phone ñ 0121 202 0000
By Letter ñ FAO Data Protection Officer, Box Ltd, First
Avenue, Minworth, Sutton Coldfield, B76 1BA
In Person - Box Ltd, First Avenue, Minworth, Sutton
Coldfield, B76 1BA
Compare
Maximum of 4 Products
Compare Products >
You can pay with:
Certified:
We deliver with:
Got a question? Contact us:
Need Help?
Need Help?
+
Frequently asked questions
Contact us
Sign up to Box news
How to find us
Delivery information
Returns information
Klarna FAQ
Influencer Partnerships
Representative Example: Purchase rate 19.9% p.a. (variable) | Representative 19.9% APR (variable) | Assumed Credit Limit £1,200
Credit subject to Status. Terms and Conditions apply. Box Limited acts as a broker and offers credit from PayPal Credit
Box Limited is authorised and regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority. Our registration number is OFT 626739
PayPal Credit is a trading name of PayPal (Europe) S.‡.r.l. et Cie, S.C.A., 22-24 Boulevard Royal L-2449, Luxembourg. Klarna Bank AB (publ) is Authorised by the Swedish Financial Services Authority (Finansinspektionen) and is subject to limited regulation by the Financial Conduct Authority. Details about the extent of our regulation by the Financial Conduct Authority are available from us on request. Finance is only available to permanent UK residents aged >18, subject to status, terms and conditions apply. Registered office: Sveav√§gen 46, 111 34 Stockholm, Sweden. Corporation ID number: 556737-0431.
Intel, the Intel Logo, Intel Inside, Intel Core, and Core Inside are trademarks of Intel Corporation in the U.S. and/or other countries.
Copyright © 1996-2020 Box Ltd | Terms and Conditions
Switch to Desktop view
Switch to Mobile view
Box.co.uk uses cookies to deliver and improve the website experience.
See our privacy policy for further details on how we use cookies and how to change your cookie settings.
Accept
